Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors but lower
in calories and higher in protein. This
is coffee coffee buzz buzz buzz. Let me
show you how to make it. We are starting
off with a classic coffee base. So that
involves some high protein milk, vanilla
bean paste, sweetener, salt, zantham
gum, and then some kind of coffee
flavoring. I used a Cometier coffee
concentrate pod, but you can also use
instant coffee, espresso, or some other
kind of coffee concentrate. Then you
just need to blend it all together.
Throw it in the freezer for at least 16
hours. Take it out, run under hot water
for about a minute, and then throw it in
your creamy on the light ice cream
setting. While it's spinning, you can
grab your chocolatecovered espresso
beans. I just found some generic ones
from my local grocery store. Chop those
up into your desired size and then throw
them in as a mixin. These actually work
super well as a mixin. You get a little
bit of the crunchiness from the espresso
bean and then the chocolate kind of
turns into little fudge flakes. And I
honestly think this recipe tastes just
as good as Ben and Jerry's version. So
give it a shot and let me know what you
think.